<FILE><TITLE>Pseudomonas aeruginosa infection in cystic fibrosis.  Occurrence of
precipitating antibodies against pseudomonas aeruginosa in relation
to the concentration of sixteen serum proteins and the clinical and
radiographical status of the lungs.</TITLE><TITLE>Amylase content of mixed saliva in children.</TITLE><TITLE>A clinical study of the diagnosis of cystic fibrosis by instrumental
neutron activation analysis of sodium in nail clippings.</TITLE><TITLE>A methodological study of the diagnosis of cystic fibrosis by
instrumental neutron activation analysis of sodium in nail clippings.</TITLE><TITLE>Proteolytic activity in duodenal juice in infants, children, and
adults.</TITLE><TITLE>Pseudomonas aeruginosa infection in cystic fibrosis.  Distribution
of B and T lymphocytes in relation to the humoral immune response.</TITLE><TITLE>Pseudomonas aeruginosa infection in cystic fibrosis.  Relationship
between mucoid strains of Pseudomonas aeruginosa and the humoral
immune response.</TITLE><TITLE>Epidemiological investigations of the respiratory tract bacteriology
in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>The occurrence of cystic fibrosis and celiac sprue within a single
sibship.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in a patient with Kartagener syndrome.</TITLE><TITLE>Coexistent respiratory allergy and cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Silver-Russell dwarfism and cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in blacks in Washington, DC: incidence and
characteristics.</TITLE><TITLE>Present status of intrauterine diagnosis of genetic defects.</TITLE><TITLE>Polypoid cervicitis in cystic fibrosis patients receiving oral
contraceptives.</TITLE><TITLE>Ataxia-telangiectasia: chronic pneumonia, sinusitis, and adenoidal
hypoplasia.</TITLE><TITLE>Pulmonary involvement in adults with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Selective inhibition of phagocytic activity of rabbit
alveolar macrophages by cystic fibrosis serum.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Plasma arginine esterase activity in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>The relative sensitivity of closing volume in children with asthma
and cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Bronchial asthma and allergic rhinitis associated with inhalation of
pancreatic extracts.</TITLE><TITLE>Specific airway resistance from the perinatal period into adulthood.
Alterations in childhood pulmonary disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Human respiratory tract secretions.  1. Mucous glycoproteins
secreted by cultured nasal polyp epithelium from subjects with
allergic rhinitis and with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Lung elastic recoil in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Use of water vapor in the treatment of lower respiratory disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Plasma arginine esterase activity in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Pulmonary physiotherapy in the pediatric age group.</TITLE><TITLE>Studies on neutron activation analysis for the measurement of sodium
in nails as a screening test for cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Upper respiratory tract in cystic fibrosis.  Ear-nose-throat survey
of 50 children.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Muscular performance and vitamin E in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Influence of mist tent therapy on sputum viscosity and water content
in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Chronic suppurative lung disease in sisters mimicking cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Plasma proteins in meconium from normal infants and from babies with
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Cystic fibrosis and coeliac disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Immunochemical method for detection of albumin in human meconium.</TITLE><TITLE>Proceedings: Neonatal peritonitis.</TITLE><TITLE>Proceedings: Experience with an ion-specific electrode to measure
sweat chloride.</TITLE><TITLE>Screening for cystic fibrosis by examination of meconium.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in 3 Pakistani children.</TITLE><TITLE>Ultrastructure of the in vitro formation of hydroxyapatite in
submandibular saliva of children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Paneth cell metaplasia in diseases of the colon and rectum.</TITLE><TITLE>Anosmic hypogonadotropic hypogonadism Kallman's syndrome--a case
history complicated by cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Family response to cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: effect of media from cultured cystic fibrosis
fibroblasts on ATPase activity.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: demonstration of an abnormality in
mucopolysaccharides in cultured lymphoid lines.</TITLE><TITLE>Hereditary disorders of intestinal transport.</TITLE><TITLE>The elasticity of sputum at low shear rates.</TITLE><TITLE>Immunological studies in children with cystic fibrosis (C.F.).</TITLE><TITLE>Comparative trial of pancrex V forte and nutrizym in treatment of
malabsorption in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Failure of bronchopulmonary lavage in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>The levels of galactosyltransferase activity in sera from normal
children and patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Erythrocyte membrane properties in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Properties of microsomal glycoprotein galactosyltransferase of
cultured human fibroblasts in relation to cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Ca2+ uptake and binding by isolated erythrocyte membranes from
cystic fibrosis and control subjects.</TITLE><TITLE>Some aspects of immunity in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Differential diagnosis of wheezing in children.  Remarks based on a
postgraduate lecture.</TITLE><TITLE>Glucose intolerance in a three-year-old child with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Chronic sinusitis in children.  Comments on pathogenesis and
management.</TITLE><TITLE>Serum alkaline phosphatase in cystic fibrosis.  Interpretation of
elevated values based on electrophoretic isoenzyme analyses.</TITLE><TITLE>Differential diagnosis of childhood asthma.</TITLE><TITLE>Tobramycin therapy of pulmonary infections in patients with cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Serum protein paper electrophoresis in cystic fibrosis correlated
with bacteriological lung findings.</TITLE><TITLE>Serum protein paper electrophoresis in cystic fibrosis correlated
with clinical and radiological findings.</TITLE><TITLE>Lung function in children and young adults with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Screening for cystic fibrosis with chloride electrode.  An
investigation of sweat chloride with chloride electrode orion 417 in
normal persons and in patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Diminished excretion of bicarbonate from the single sweat gland of
patients with cystic fibrosis of the pancreas.</TITLE><TITLE>The expression of inherited metabolic disease in cultured cells.</TITLE><TITLE>Hematological findings in Greek children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Clinical variations of cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Use of a semi-synthetic amino acid, 3-methoxyphenyl-L-alanine to
measure amino acid absorption.  pp.  304-6.</TITLE><TITLE>Studies of alpha1-antitrypsin in amniotic fluid, meconium and cord
serum of a homozygote newborn infant.  pp.  107-22.</TITLE><TITLE>Advances in the diagnosis of human genetic disorders.  pp.  297-317.</TITLE><TITLE>The prevalence of coeliac disease and cystic fibrosis in Ireland,
Scotland, England and Wales.</TITLE><TITLE>Cytoplasmic metachromasia in cultured skin fibroblasts from parents
of children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Prediction of tetracycline-induced tooth discoloration.</TITLE><TITLE>Problems affecting the community.  Population screening.</TITLE><TITLE>Standardization of a new minor salivary gland collecting procedure
for the diagnosis of cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Intracisternal inclusion bodies induced in animals: their
transformation and significance.</TITLE><TITLE>Pyocin typing of Pseudomonas aeruginosa.</TITLE><TITLE>Pseudomonas aeruginosa infection and humoral antibody response of
patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Role of antibody in infections due to Pseudomonas aeruginosa.</TITLE><TITLE>Preliminary investigations of Pseudomonas aeruginosa vaccine in
patients with leukemia and cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Cellular metachromasia with toluidine blue O in cultured
white cells of cystic fibrosis heterozygotes.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: current concepts.</TITLE><TITLE>Effects of cystic fibrosis sera on Proteus vulgaris motility.</TITLE><TITLE>Evolution of plasmids in vivo in a strain of Staphylococcus aureus.</TITLE><TITLE>Radionuclide evaluation of regional lung function in children.</TITLE><TITLE>Staphylococcus aureus empyema in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Steatorrhea and azotorrhea and their relation to growth and
nutrition in adolescents and young adults with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Editorial: Mists and aerosols: new studies, new thoughts.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Effect of antibiotics on sweat chloride levels in cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Endocrine function of the pancreas in cystic fibrosis: evidence for
an impaired glucagon and insulin response following arginine
infusion.</TITLE><TITLE>Pulmonary deposition of aerosols in children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Cystic fibrosis with edema and falsely negative sweat test.</TITLE><TITLE>Abdominal complaints and appendiceal changes leading to the
diagnosis of cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Familial meconium ileus not associated with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Hypoproteinemia and anemia in infants with cystic fibrosis.  A
presenting symptom complex often misdiagnosed.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Idiopathic hypoproteinemia in twins.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis manifested as focal biliary cirrhosis in a newborn
infant with congenital heart disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Medical mucoid lesions of the pulmonary artery in cystic fibrosis,
pulmonary hypertension, and other disorders.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Treatment of cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Complement components in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Skin wrinkling in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Frequency of cystic-fibrosis gene.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Skin wrinkling in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Sulphate incorporation of leucocytes from patients with
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Complement components in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Increased uptake of 35S-heparin by lymphocytes from patients with
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Wrinkling of skin in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Nitroblue-tetrazolium test in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Bioassays of cystic-fibrosis factor.</TITLE><TITLE>Intelligence after malnutrition caused by neonatal resection of
ileum.</TITLE><TITLE>Invertebrate model for study of macromolecular regulators of mucus
secretion.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Skin wrinkling and nerve function.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Skin wrinkling in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Fetal malformations and abnormalities.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: White-cell glutathione reductase in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Skin wrinkling in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Inherited metabolic disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Uptake of 35S-heparin by lymphocytes from cystic-fibrosis
patients.</TITLE><TITLE>Studies on ciliary dyskinesia factor in cystic fibrosis.  IV.  Its
possible identification as anaphylatoxin (C3a)-IgG complex.</TITLE><TITLE>Inhibition of Pseudomonas aeruginosa by ascorbic acid acting singly
and in combination with antimicrobials: in-vitro and in-vivo studies.</TITLE><TITLE>Number of ouabain-binding sites in fibroblasts from normal subjects
and patients with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Na+ transport defect in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Essential fatty acids in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>A screening tool to detect psychosocial adjustment of children with
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Home care for CF patients.</TITLE><TITLE>Bile acid malabsorption in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis in black population.</TITLE><TITLE>Rapid semiquantitative tests for trypsin and chymotrypsin
application to screening for cystic fibrosis, enterokinase
deficiency and pancreatic hypoplasia in neonates.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>The use of medium-chain triglyceride in children with intestinal
malabsorption.</TITLE><TITLE>Chronic diarrhea in childhood: a new look at an old problem.</TITLE><TITLE>Cystic fibrosis: a not-so-fatal disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Chronic illness in adolescents.</TITLE><TITLE>Standardized assay for the sodium reabsorption inhibitory effect and
studies of its salivary gland distribution in patients with cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>An evaluation of differential methylation of ribonucleic acid in
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Purification and properties of the calcium-precipitable protein in
submaxillary saliva of normal and cystic fibrosis subjects.</TITLE><TITLE>Erythrocyte transport function in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Arginine esterase in cystic fibrosis of the pancreas.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Cystic fibrosis ciliary inhibitor.</TITLE><TITLE>The methylation of transfer and ribosomal ribonucleic acid in human
fibroblasts: normal methylation of ribonucleic acid in cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Helium flow-volume curves in the detection of early small airway
disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Intellectual development after severe malnutrition in infancy.</TITLE><TITLE>Outpatient intravenous medications in the management of cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Letter: Rates and calcium concentrations of sweat in relation to
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Severe respiratory disease in infants with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Liver-spleen scanning in pediatrics.</TITLE><TITLE>Use of serum amylase isoenzymes in evaluation of pancreatic function.</TITLE><TITLE>The electron microscopic appearance of presecreted gastric mucus in
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Gentamicin in paediatrics.</TITLE><TITLE>Therapeutic special diets.</TITLE><TITLE>Defects in the cell cycle of fibroblasts obtained from patients with
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Quantitative assessment of regional ventilation and perfusion in
children with cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Endoscopic pancreatography: an analysis of the radiologic findings
in pancreatitis.</TITLE><TITLE>Vitamin E: who needs it?.</TITLE><TITLE>Analysis of albumin in meconium for early detection of cystic
fibrosis.  A methodological study.</TITLE><TITLE>Tobramycin treatment of pseudomonas aeruginosa infections in cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>The patterns of infection in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Susceptibility of mucoid Pseudomonas aeruginosa to gentamicin disks.</TITLE><TITLE>Some materials on the genetics of mucoviscidosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Abnormal thyroid function and response to iodides in patients with
cystic fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>Whole cell heat-killed gram-negative bacilli vaccine.</TITLE><TITLE>The determination of vitamin A and some aspects of its distribution,
mobilization and transport in health and disease.</TITLE><TITLE>Histochemical observations on the pulmonary macrophages in cystic
fibrosis.</TITLE><TITLE>HL-A antigens in cystic fibrosis.</TITLE></FILE>